Akshay and welcome, ready with us, keep a
close eye on this occasion and
according to the appointment news, there
is news related to Monday that the way
we have seen growth in this financial year till February
26 as compared to last year
and I have
received information from sources that
in the process of bidding related to the line
and there are two options either to
buy the entire company or
there is
capital subsidy for buying the subsidiary of Reliance Capital, the general insurance
company buys Reliance General Insurance Company,
in this process, it will move towards
becoming the number one general insurance company of the country,
right now the market share of
Reliance General Insurance till February is
around 4 percent, so if it keeps increasing,
it will become close to 26
percent in a short time and the top
market leader, New India Assurance, right now its
market share is 15
percent, but we will see the
growth it has been showing since the last some time, after this look, the
innovations and initiatives taken by them, then it is
moving very fast and long ahead of
26 percent.  Look at the growth,
in such a body, till February last year, their
premium of Rs 13000 crore has increased
to Rs 16000 crore, so if
this is the way the news is that
ICICI Lombard has bid in the IPC
process of Reliance Capital
and takes over Reliance's general
insurance company Reliance General Insurance, if it is done in this way then there will be a
huge development and ICICI Lombard will
become the number one general insurance company of the country,
okay, then the
market share will increase, you
can see that in the next 10-12 percent,
absolutely, this number one company,
which has
something in the market, as much as they are showing, they are not able to sleep,
with the technology advancement, it has not been done, that has
not happened
yet, they do not have time, the last four months have been given, it is
not expected for the next several months, there
are issues related to the salaries of the employees, the government
wants to do this, so that is also a question
and whatever is there is related to it, but on the
contrary, it is moving very fast
that the
war and
Subscribe at midnight
properly
that
I am on general insurance so I am so much police
news channel hum log hai life more
election but with his pace if this
youth has to wait for
insurance because
gradually the company is paying
attention to its head and most of the
etc. etc. has happened so in the coming time there
should be some increase in it so please